secretdate.com 2018-12-26

# Privacy statement

The Privacy Policy applies to all users/participants related to www.secretdate.com.

## 1\. Operation

The website www.secretdate.com is managed by Next Step Media BV, hereinafter referred to as: “Next Step Media.” This organization is also responsible for recording and processing any provided and used data.

## 2\. Purpose behind data recording

Next Step Media processes the personal data provided by you for the following purposes: 

  * The formation and implementation of the agreement between you and Next Step Media
  * Billing purposes when using a paid service or product 
  * In order to send you a service message or newsletter via e-mail
  * To display targeted ads and for the creation of commercial mailings
  * In order to comply with laws and regulations applicable to Next Step Media

## 3\. Provision of information to third parties

It is possible that Next Step Media involves third parties within the framework of the execution of its services. If said party (parties) thereby gain access to your personal information, they will process this information solely to serve Next Step Media. Your data (different from the data that make up your profile and contact information) will not be provided to third parties without your permission, unless Next Step Media is bound to provide certain information. For example, with law enforcement within the context of a criminal investigation. 

## 4\. Data protection

Next Step Media ensures that any registered personal data will be kept confidential and is treated with the utmost care. All personal data is securely stored in a database that is only accessible to persons for whom it is essential they have access to this data as deemed necessary due to of their position within the company. Next Step Media is (within reason) committed to securing its systems against loss and/or any form of unlawful use. However, Next Step Media is not responsible for any loss of data, any damage to files, or any unlawful access to files.

## 5\. Transfer of operations

If the operations of Next Step Media or any parts thereof are purchased by or merged with another company, personal data relating to you may be part of such a transaction and will therefore be considered one of the acquired assets.

## 6\. Amendments

Next Step Media has the right to modify this Privacy Policy unilaterally. Any changes will be announced on the website. We advise you to refer to our privacy statement regularly.
